James A. Baker III Papers, 1957-2011 (bulk 1972-1992): Finding Aid MC197
Public Policy Papers
- Series 11: Speeches and Interviews, 1952-1995; 29 boxes
  - Subseries 11D. Secretary of the Treasury, 1952-1989; 11 boxes
    - World Trade Expo Dinner (Los Angeles, CA), 1986 October 19; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 25)
    - First-Struck U.S. Liberty Coins (Liberty Island, New York), 1986 October 28; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 26)
    - American Eagle Silver Bullion Coin San Francisco Assay Office/U.S. Mint, 1986 October 29; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 27)
    - Preservation of the Treasury Cash Room (Main Treasury), 1986 November 3; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 28)
    - Association of Federal Investigators (Washington, D.C.), 1986 November 6; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 29)
    - Federal Law Enforcement Training Center (Glynco, GA), 1986 November 17; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 30)
    - Remarks to the Asia Society (Washington, D.C.), 1986 November 18; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 31)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (New York City, New York), 1986 November 20; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 32)
    - 1987 Combined Federal Campaign Victory Luncheon (Washington, D.C.), 1986 November 25, 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 33)
    - Southern Methodist University (Dallas), 1986 December 2; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 34)
    - Dallas Chapter of the Young Presidents' Organization (Dallas), 1986 December 2; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 35)
    - International Management and Development Institute (Washington, D.C.), 1986 December 3; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 36)
    - Luncheon for Members of New York Investment Banking Community, 1986 December 4; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Summit on Trade and Debt (New York City, New York), 1986 December 4; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - National Symphony Luncheon, Cash Room, Treasury Department (Washington, D.C.), 1986 December 6; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Savings Bond Volunteer Committee, Department of State (Washington, D.C.), 1986 December 10; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Savings Bond Annual Luncheon, Department of State (Washington, D.C.), 1986 December 10; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Economic Club, 1986 December 11; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Address Ambassadors' Roundtable (Washington, D.C.), 1986 December 16; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Press Briefing on Fiscal Year 1988 Budget Government Printing Office Auditorium (Washington, D.C.), 1987 January 5, 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Statement Before the Senate Budget Committee, 1987 January 8; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Address the Garn Institute (Washington, D.C.), 1987 January 12; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Swearing-In Ceremony for L. Gibbs and W. Nelson (Treasury Building), 1987 January 16; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - 125th Anniversary of the Bureau of Engraving and Printing (The Annex Building), 1987 January 29; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia Economic Club, 1987 January 29; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Joint Economic Committee/Testimony, 1987 January 30; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - 10th Meeting of U.S./Saudi Joint Commission (Riyadh, Saudi Arabia), 1987 February 3; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Dinner with Minister Abalkhail (Riyadh, Saudi Arabia), 1987 February 3; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - American Businessmen's Group of Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, 1987 February 3; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - U.S./Saudi Joint Commission on Economic Cooperation (Riyadh, Saudi Arabia), 1987 February 4; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - House Ways and Means Testimony/Trade (Capitol Hill, Washington, D.C.), 1987 February 10; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Address at American University Kennedy Political Union Lecture Series (Washington, D.C.), 1987 February 10; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - Presidential Rank Awards, Treasury Executive Institute, 1987 February 12; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - Luncheon for Business Leaders, The White House (Washington, D.C.), 1987 February 17; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 22)
    - Competitiveness Initiative Kickoff, The White House (Washington, D.C.), 1987 February 17; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 23)
    - Bipartisan Leadership Breakfast with Members of House and Senate, 1987 February 18; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 24)
    - 1987 Savings Bond Luncheon (New York City, New York), 1987 February 18, 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 25)
    - Testimony before the Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, 1987 February 24; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 26)
    - Northeast-Midwest Leadership Council (Washington, D.C.), 1987 February 25; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 27)
    - Testimony before Senate Appropriations Committee, 1987 February 26; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 28)
    - American Association of Retired Persons (Washington, D.C.), 1987 February 27; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 29)
    - Semper Fidelis Award Presentation, J.W. Marriott (Washington, D.C.), 1987 February 28; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 30)
    - Arrival Statement (Rabat, Morocco), 1987 March 2; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 31)
    - Departure Statement (Rabat, Morocco), 1987 March 5; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 32)
    - National Newspaper Association (Washington, D.C.), 1987 March 6; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 33)
    - National Council of Savings Institutions, J.W. Marriott Hotel (Washington, D.C.), 1987 March 10; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 34)
    - National Fitness Foundation Dinner (New York City, New York), 1987 March 11; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Statement before Subcommittee on Foreign Operations/House Appropriations Committee, 1987 March 17; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Cash Management Ceremony, Department of Commerce, 1987 March 25; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Bank Secrecy Act/Related Developments (Taping Session), 1987 March 25; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Texan of the Year Ceremony (New Braunfels, Texas), 1987 March 26; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Texas Legislative Conference (New Braunfels, Texas), 1987 March 27; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - House Appropriations Committee, 1987 March 31; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - New York Stock Exchange Board of Directors (National Gallery of Art), 1987 April 1; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Subcommittee on Treasury, Postal Service, General Government, 1987 April 1; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Bush for President State Finance Chairman Conference, Westin Hotel (Washington, D.C.), 1987 April 4; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Interim and Development Committee Meetings (Washington, D.C.), 1987 April 9-10; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Development Committee of the International Monetary Fund and World Bank, Morning Session (Washington, D.C.), 1987 April 10; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Development Committee of the International Monetary Fund and World Bank (Washington, D.C.), 1987 April 10; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - 31st Evans/Novak Political Forum (Washington, D.C.), 1987 April 15; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Annual Dinner of the Japan Society (New York City, New York), 1987 April 15; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - House Republican Research Committee Luncheon (Washington, D.C.), 1987 April 23; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - American Enterprise Institute Conference on Competitiveness and Trade, L'Enfant Plaza Hotel (Washington, D.C.), 1987 April 24; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Businessmen's Breakfast with Congressman Dick Armey (Dallas), 1987 April 25; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony for Currency Plant (Ft. Worth, Texas), 1987 April 25; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - Rice University President's Executive Luncheon (Houston, Texas), 1987 April 27; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Remarks before Constituents of Representatives Lott and Oxley (Washington, D.C.), 1987 May 4; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - Macroeconomic Policy Outlook, Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development Ministerial (Paris, France), 1987 May 12; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Structural Adjustment at Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (Paris, France), 1987 May 13; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 23)
    - Anglo-American Press Association (Paris, France), 1987 May 13; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 24)
    - Opening Statement/Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development Ministerial (Paris, France), 1987 May 13; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 25)
    - American Chamber of Commerce (Paris, France), 1987 May 14; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 26)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute (Washington, D.C.), 1987 May 20; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - Chicago World Trade Conference, 1987 May 21; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 28)
    - University of Texas Law School Commencement (Austin, Texas), 1987 May 24; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 29)
    - Videotaping at University of Texas (Austin, Texas), 1987 May; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 30)
    - James Bayless Distinguished Speaker (Houston, Texas), 1987 May 26; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 31)
    - Briefing Hearst Newspaper Editors, Mayflower Hotel (Washington, D.C.), 1987 June 1; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 32)
    - Briefing for Diplomats and American Foreign Policy Experts, White House East Room (Washington, D.C.), 1987 June 1; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 33)
    - Pre-Summit Briefing for White House Press Corps (Washington, D.C.), 1987 June 2; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 34)
    - Announcement of A. Greenspan as New Chairman of the Federal Reserve Board, White House Press Briefing Room, 1987 June 2; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 35)
    - Pan American Economic Leadership Conference (Indianapolis, IN), 1987 June 15; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 36)
    - Bipartisan Congressional Leadership Meeting, Cabinet Room, 1987 June 15; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 37)
    - Post-1987 Summit Briefing for Out-of-Town Reporters (White House), 1987 June 16; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 38)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies Washington Quarterly Roundtable, 1987 June 16; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Senate Seminar of Senator John Heinz (Washington, D.C.), 1987 June 18; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Ceremony Honoring Combined Federal Campaign Fundraising Efforts (Treasury), 1987 June 18; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Edward W. Kelley Swearing-In as a Member of Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve (Washington, D.C.), 1987 June 18; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - National Federation of Independent Business(Washington, D.C.), 1987 June 22; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Annual Awards Ceremony for Departmental Employees (Treasury), 1987 June 25; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Health and Human Services Conference on Retiree Health Care Benefits, Mayflower Hotel (Washington, D.C.), 1987 June 25; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia Mint First Strike of Constitution Coin, 1987 July 1; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - 125th Anniversary Internal Revenue Service, 1987 July 14; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - National Youth Science Camp (Washington, D.C.), 1987 July 15; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Dinner Honoring Paul A. Volcker (Washington, D.C.), 1987 July 28; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - 4th World Wilderness Congress (Denver, CO), 1987 September 11; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Conference "Institute for International Economics" (Washington, D.C.), 1987 September 14; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Ed Madigan Fundraiser (Illinois), 1987 September 18; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Joint Meetings of International Monetary Fund/World Bank (Washington, D.C.), 1987 September 30; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Conference "Tax Policy in the 21st Century" (Washington, D.C.), 1987 October 6; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - United States Information Agency International Council, Old Executive Office Building (Washington, D.C.), 1987 October 9; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - White House Economic Briefing, 1987 October 15; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Dinner in Honor of Chinese Delegation (Washington, D.C.), 1987 November 16; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Princeton University Associates, Willard Hotel (Washington, D.C.), 1987 December 1; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency (Washington, D.C.), 1987 December 3; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - Dinner with Prime Minister Goria, Ambassador's Residence, 1987 December 16; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - Texas GOP Fundraiser (Dallas), 1988 January 14; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - Prayer for National Prayer Breakfast (Washington, D.C.), 1988 February 4; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 24)
    - Headliners Club (Austin, Texas), 1988 February 5; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 25)
    - National Cotton Council of America (Memphis, TN), 1988 February 8; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 26)
    - Testimony before Subcommittee on Trade (Capitol Hill), 1988 February 9; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 27)
    - 1987 Presidential Rank Awards (Ariel Rios Federal Building), 1988 February 11, 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 28)
    - Bretton Woods Committee Annual Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1988 February 16; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 29)
    - Press Briefing on President's 1989 Budget, 1988 February 18, 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 30)
    - Lunch with Foreign Minister Choi, Not Used (Seoul, Korea), 1988 February 25; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 31)
    - Departure Statement (Seoul, Korea), 1988 February 26; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 32)
    - Testimony before Senate Appropriations Committee (Washington, D.C.), 1988 March 1; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 33)
    - Testimony before Senate Budget Committee (Washington, D.C.), 1988 March 4; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 34)
    - Testimony before the Joint Economic Committee (Washington, D.C.), 1988 March 9; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - 69th Meeting of Spartanburg Chamber of Commerce (Spartanburg, SC), 1988 March 10; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Washington Representatives of Corporations and Trade Associations (White House), 1988 March 11; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Texas Women's Alliance Conference (Austin, Texas), 1988 March 14; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - House Appropriations Testimony (Washington, D.C.), 1988 March 15; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - National Meeting of World Economic Forum (Washington, D.C.), 1988 March 22; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - 4th Annual Awards Ceremony/Commerce Department (Washington, D.C.), 1988 March 23; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Center for the Study of the President (Washington, D.C.), 1988 March 24; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Testimony before the Subcommittee on Foreign Operations (Washington, D.C.), 1988 March 30; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Political Speech (Grand Rapids, MI), 1988 March 30; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Political Speech (Detroit, MI), 1988 March 30; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Meeting of Business and Industry Association (Manchester, NH), 1988 April 4; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Treasury Preservation Fund Dinner, 1988 April 5; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Farewell Party for D. Edward Wilson Jr. and Jane Kratovil, 1988 April 6; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Fordham University/Graduate School of Business (New York City, New York), 1988 April 7; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Princeton Class of 1952 (Washington, D.C.), 1988 April 9, 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Development Committee – International Monetary Fund/World Bank, Morning Session (Washington, D.C.), 1988 April 15; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Subcommittee on Treasury/Postal/General Government (Senate), 1988 April 18; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Statement before the Subcommittee on Treasury/Postal/General Government (House), 1988 April 19; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Canadian Club of Ottawa (Ontario, Canada), 1988 April 21; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Fundraiser for Congressman Mac Sweeney (Austin, Texas), 1988 April 22; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - Briefing for Congressman Thomas Tauke (Rayburn House Office Building), 1988 April 25; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Open House for Executive Committee for Excellence (Main Treasury/Cash Room), 1988 April 26; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - Senator Tim Wirth's 14th Annual Seminar (Dirksen Senate Office Building), 1988 April 28; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 24)
    - Subcommittee on Foreign Operations (Washington, D.C.), 1988 April 28; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 25)
    - U.S. Marine Corps Education Center (Quantico, VA), 1988 April 29; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - 1st Strike Ceremony-U.S. Olympic Coins (Denver, CO), 1988 May 2; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 27)
    - Congressman Bill Michel of Illinois Briefing (Washington, D.C.), 1988 May 3; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 28)
    - Economic Club of Detroit (Detroit, MI), 1988 May 9; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 29)
    - Congressman Carl Pursell, Support (Ann Arbor, MI), 1988 May 9; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 30)
    - The President's Dinner, Willard Hotel (Washington, D.C.), 1988 May 11; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 31)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies (Washington, D.C.), 1988 May 12; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 32)
    - 54th Commencement Program, University of Houston (Houston), 1988 May 14; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 33)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Paris, France), 1988 May 20; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 34)
    - Congressman Bill McCollum Constituents (Washington, D.C.), 1988 May 23; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 35)
    - Harmonie Club (New York City, New York), 1988 May 24; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 36)
    - Congressman Silvio Conte Constituents (Washington, D.C.), 1988 May 25; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Republican Members of 100th Congress (Washington, D.C.), 1988 May 25; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Press Conference (Dakar, Senegal), 1988 May 30; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Central Bank for West African States (Dakar, Senegal), 1988 May 30; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meetings of the African Development Bank and Fund (Abidjan, Cote d'Ivoire), 1988 June 1; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - American Chamber of Commerce (Abidjan, Cote d'Ivoire), 1988 June 2; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Press Conference (Abidjan, Cote d'Ivoire), 1988 June 2; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - 1988 International Monetary Conference (Chicago, IL), 1988 June 6, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Headliner Breakfast (Capitol Hill, D.C.), 1988 June 8; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Summit County Republican Dinner (Summit County, OH), 1988 June 8; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Mid-American Committee and Canadian Business Council (Chicago, IL), 1988 June 13; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs (Washington, D.C.), 1988 June 15; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Pre-Summit Briefing (White House), 1988 June 15; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Meeting of Princeton Club of Washington (Washington, D.C.), 1988 June 16; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - U.S.I.A. International Council Briefing (Washington, D.C.), 1988 June 16; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - American Coalition for Trade Expansion (Washington, D.C.), 1988 June 16; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Canadian Importers and Exporters Association (Toronto, Ontario), 1988 June 22; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Fundraiser, Congressman Gradison (Cincinnati, OH), 1988 July 8; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Fundraiser, Pete Wilson (Los Angeles, CA), 1988 July 23; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Resignation as Secretary of Treasury White House Remarks, 1988 August 5; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - Resignation as Secretary of Treasury White House Remarks/Remarks at George Bush for President Campaign, 1988 August 5; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - Remarks, 1988 November; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Speech Notes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - Major Policy Statements -- Treasury, 1985-87, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - General Remarks for Political Fundraisers, 1986; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 26)
    - Statement to the International Monetary Fund Interim Committee Regarding G-10 and G-24 Reports (Not Used), undated; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 27)
  - Subseries 11E. Secretary of State, 1989-1992; 15 boxes
    The Secretary of State subseries contains speeches, testimony, remarks, press briefing material, and interviews made during Baker's term as Secretary of State. Speeches in this subseries include remarks made in conjunction with foreign officials, testimony before Congress, various swearing-in ceremonies, and press conferences. Unlike the Chief of Staff and Treasury speeches, the Secretary of State speeches also include interviews transcripts from Baker's appearances on various news programs
    Speech files are arranged chronologically, with general State Department speech material located at the end of the subseries.
    - Testimony Before Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1989 January 17; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 28)
    - Remarks After Taking Oath of Office as Secretary of State (White House), 1989 January 27; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Remarks to Response Strategies Working Group (Department of State), 1989 January 30; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Toast at Dinner Hosted by Ambassador/Mrs. Matsunaga for Prime Minister/Mrs. Takeshita, 1989 February 2; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Toast at Luncheon for Japan Prime Minister and Mrs. Takeshita (Department of State), 1989 February 3; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Statement on Peace and Relief in Sudan (Department of State), 1989 February 8; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Remarks in Conjunction with Travel to NATO Capitals, 1989 February 10-17; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - NBC "Meet the Press" Interview (Washington, D.C.), 1989 February 2; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Testimony Before House Foreign Affairs Committee (Washington, D.C.), 1989 February 21; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Remarks in Conjunction with Travel with President to Tokyo (Tokyo, Japan), 1989 February 22-27; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Remarks in Conjunction with Travel to Vienna (Vienna, Austria), 1989 March 4-7, 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Remarks Introducing President Bush at Wilson Center Dinner (Department of State), 1989 March 7; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Testimony Before House Appropriations Subcommittee, 1989 March 9; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Remarks with Israel Foreign Minister Arens (Department of State), 1989 March 13; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Testimony Before House Appropriations Subcommittee on Foreign Affairs, 1989 March 14; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Remarks at Swearing-In Ceremony for Robert Kimmitt (State Department), 1989 March 14; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Testimony Before Senate Appropriations Subcommittee on Foreign Affairs, 1989 March 15; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Thank-You Remarks to Traveling Support Staff (Treaty Room), 1989 March 17; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Testimony Before House Foreign Affairs Subcommittee, 1989 March 21; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Remarks at Memorial Service for John J. McCloy (New York City, New York), 1989 March 21; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Remarks Before State of Israel Bonds, 1989 March 23; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 20)
    - Joint News Conference (Briefing Room), 1989 March 24; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - "MacNeil-Lehrer Newshour" Interview (Washington, D.C.), 1989 March 24; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 22)
    - ABC "This Week With David Brinkley" Interview, 1989 March 26; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 23)
    - NBC "Today Show" Interview (Houston), 1989 March 27; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 24)